https://www.afao.org.au/terms-and-copyright/

Terms and Copyrightadmin2020-01-29T08:41:49+10:30
Terms and Copyright
Australian Federation of AIDS Organisations – Website General Terms of Use and Copyright
1  General Terms of Use
1.1  This page sets out the terms of use of this website, including the use of the information provided on this website (“General Terms of Use”).
1.2  These General Terms of Use apply to the website (afao.org.au) owned and operated by the Australian Federation of AIDS Organisations Limited (ABN 91 708 310 631) (“AFAO”, “we”, “us” or “our”).
1.3  By using this website, you accept all of its terms (including these General Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy).
1.4  We reserve the right to update or amend these General Terms of Use at any time. You should check this page from time to time to make sure you are aware of any changes.
2  Website content
2.1  We use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the information we provide on this website is accurate at the date of publication, however, we cannot guarantee the accuracy, currency or completeness of the information provided.
2.2  We use reasonable efforts to ensure you can access and use our website at all times. However, we do not guarantee that use of our website will be uninterrupted or error-free, or that materials accessible on or through the website will be free from errors, viruses, worms or other harmful code.
2.3  The appearance of models on the website is not to be construed as a representation of their sexuality or HIV status, or the sexuality or HIV status of their friends, family or acquaintances.
2.4  While all medical and scientific information provided on these pages is subject to technical review before publication, information may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. We accept no responsibility for errors in the content at any time. Further, the content on this website is not provided as medical advice, and should not be considered a substitute for medical advice and treatment by qualified health professionals.
2.5  AFAO uses reasonable endeavours to provide high quality information about HIV treatment and prevention strategies. While the information may assist you with your decision-making, you should not act on the basis of any content contained on this website without first obtaining professional advice specific to your circumstances. The choice of whether and when to start HIV treatment and what treatments to take, or an intervention like pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP), should be made in consultation with a general practitioner.
2.6  AFAO makes no representations, warranties or statements that the information available on the website is suitable for any particular purpose. Use of the website and its content is solely at the user’s risk, and it is the responsibility of the user to independently evaluate the website’s content.
2.7  To the extent permitted by law, all liability is excluded for any loss (including indirect loss), damages or injury resulting from your access to (or inability to access) or use of this website, or as a consequence of any content or information obtained from or through this website.
2.8  No transmission of data though an Internet website can be guaranteed as totally secure. Although we take reasonable steps to ensure the security of information in accordance with our obligations at law, we do not warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or input into forms via our website.
3  Copyright
3.1    All content contained on our website (including but not limited to all design, images, audio and video files, coding and text) is owned by or licensed to AFAO. Content is copyright © AFAO 2017, unless otherwise stated.
3.2   In recognising the fundamental importance of information and education in working against the HIV/AIDS epidemic, materials produced by AFAO may be reproduced for non-commercial, personal or educational purposes free of charge, provided that:
reproduced content must be branded AFAO and acknowledgement to AFAO must be made prominently, including a link to afao.org.au and a citation stating “Reprinted from [name of publication], published by the Australian Federation of AIDS Organisations”;
reproduced content must not be published in a manner which damages or dilutes the reputation of AFAO, or which creates a misleading impression that AFAO is associated with, or a sponsor of, the person reproducing the content; and
reproduced content must not be altered or reproduced in a misleading context.
3.3  We also work closely with committees, working parties, our member organisations and various advocacy organisations (“Agencies”). Queries regarding permission to reproduce material from our website produced by AFAO in conjunction with other Agencies, or requests regarding reproduction rights of any material for commercial purposes, should be made to AFAO directly at enquiries@afao.org.au. Reproduction of such work (or any part of such work) without the prior written consent of AFAO may be unlawful. Queries regarding permission to reproduce material from our website that is not owned by, or licensed to, AFAO (that is, any content on our website where we have stated that copyright is not vested in us) should be directed to the relevant copyright owner.
3.4  AFAO is a member of the Copyright Agency Limited (CAL). If you have been engaged by AFAO as a contributor to one of our publications in the past, we may be holding CAL funds on trust for you. If you think this may apply to you, please contact AFAO directly.
3.5  Aside from any use permitted under the Copyright Act 1968 (Cth) or under this Copyright Statement, all other rights are reserved.
4  Trade marks
4.1  This website includes trade marks which are protected by law. You may not use our trade marks in Australia or internationally without our prior written consent, except to legitimately identify our products or services.
5  Linking
5.1  You may link to any page of this website provided you do so in a way that accurately indicates that the link is to the AFAO website and is not misleading, derogatory or offensive.
6  Cookies and tracking
6.1   We may use cookies to identify your computer on our server and so that we can track your use of this website. To the extent that cookies may collect and store personal information about you, such personal information will only be used by us in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
6.2  You are able to set your browser to refuse or delete cookies. Please refer to your browser’s help information. We note that disabling cookies may limit some features of the website.
7  Third party sites
7.1   This website may contain links or references to third party sites. We use reasonable endeavours to ensure we link to third party sites that we consider reputable and therefore likely to contain up to date and accurate information about HIV and AIDS, however, we do not guarantee that this information is correct, up to date or evidence-based.
7.2  We are not responsible or liable (to any extent, or for any loss, damage, cost or expense incurred) for the content of those sites, or for the copyright or privacy practices of the sites. Your access to, and use of, those sites is at your own risk.
7.3  Any links are provided for convenience only and these links may not remain current or be maintained. The provision of links to external sites does not constitute any endorsement or recommendation by AFAO.
8  Social media
8.1  We also use a number of social media sites (such as Facebook, Twitter and YouTube) (Third Party Media Websites). These sites may change over time, and we reserve the right to cease use of any such sites at our discretion.
8.2  Your use of such Third Party Media Websites will be governed by their own specific terms of use and our pages and channels on such sites may be subject to additional terms of use.
8.3  We do not necessarily endorse, support, verify or agree with any content posted by you or any other user or member on our Third Party Media Sites. Any content uploaded or made online by you or any user or member is the view of you, or that user or member, and does not necessarily represent our view.
9  Misuse of website
9.1  You agree to only use this website in accordance with these terms and all applicable laws. You may be held personally liable for any unlawful use of this website.
9.2  You agree that you will not web scrape, harvest or crawl any of the data (including prices) on the website, either manually or by any automated technology. You further agree that you will interfere, or attempt to interfere, with the proper working of our website.
9.3  If you think any content on this website is inappropriate or unlawful or infringes your rights, please contact us at enquiries@afao.org.au.
10 Privacy
10.1  These General Terms of Use incorporate, and should be read together with, our Privacy Policy.
10.2  Any personal information collected by us through your use of this website will be dealt with in accordance with our Privacy Policy and our Privacy Collection Statement.
11  Governing law
11.1  The terms of this website will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws in force in the state of New South Wales in the Commonwealth of Australia and you unconditionally submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of New South Wales.
11.2   Although Australian websites may be accessed outside of Australia, we make no representation that the content complies with the laws of any other country. To the extent permitted by law, if you access this website from outside Australia, you are solely responsible for ensuring compliance with your local laws and for any reliance on our website content.
Last updated January 2020.
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
Been Diagnosed with HIV?
Australian Federation of AIDS Organisations (AFAO)
PO BOX 51, Newtown, NSW, Australia, 2042 | Phone: +61 (02) 9557 9399 | Email: enquiries@afao.org.au | ABN: 91 708 310 631
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
Been Diagnosed with HIV?
